No!
Jiati Mercado - Republic of Ballyvina
Bang Kang!
Bang Kang, money
of this month's deposit.
All.
Here, for you.
Thank you, Bang Kang!
Don't be fooled so
Easily tomorrow! Do it well.
I will do that.
Thank you, Bang Kang!
Hi, Kun Tai!
Why are you not here yet?
I have the money.
Hello?
Why are you so quiet?
Why did you kill my wife and daughter?
Do you want to know why?
Come with me.
Hey, do not kill the fish.
Just handle the person
That is behind me.
Okay, boss. Let's go.
Chief, boss! Nothing.
Keep eating.
OK.
Health. Health!
Because?
Why my family?
Friends,
Anyone who can kill this bastard
You will receive money from Kun Tai.
Let's go.
Everyone!
Forward!
Because?
Why did you kill me
family? They are only paying me.
To fulfill the orders of the boss.
Is Yinghao your boss?
Where can I find him? Don't know.
OK,
OK.
I just know a driver,
The boss driver.
We have seen each other a few times.
I knew about him
Yinghao picked up his daughter
In Jiati Junior High School
every day.
How many tuitions!
JII-6677.
Strike rescue
Mother!
Hello, lady,
Are you taking fighting classes
free at international school?
The atmosphere in your school is enough
exciting too! It is not yours.
Where is my father?
He is still on a business trip.
He is waiting for you at home.
You don't like it, right? He
Did as you wanted, right?
You don't have to come here.
I can go home alone.
Come on, please, go up to the car, princess!
Bored!
I'm sorry.
Are you well?
Be careful on the road.
I'm sorry.
Come!
Ting, you are at home.
Let's sit and eat.
Take it easy, surely
We will continue to support you next year.
We're sorry
Leave the sticks.
We have manners to eat.
Look your clothes.
Go change first.
Ting, let me help you.
Leave him alone.
Yinghao, something goes wrong in the
Company Logistics Department.
Police received information that
Drugs were found in our shipment.
Why?
Always drug trafficking
He has been very widespread in Jiati.
I suspect that there are some
employees in the company
collaborating in secret
With drug traffickers.
I am in charge of security control,
So you think I have a problem?
I have not said that,
But we can't say what
same of local staff.
I will investigate.
Ping lu,
If the news about
This drug extends,
There will definitely be a lot of pressure
by local authorities.
We will face a big problem
same inspection exception
Logistics at that time.
Give yourself.
Mr. He, I think our group ...
Ting.
What happens in school?
Nothing.
Nothing?
What happens to your shirt?
I just spilled paint.
So simple?
It is.
So why
director called my father and
praying that he will not withdraw
school financing?
How will I know? He
director did not report anything
To me first.
Yinghao, maybe there was a misunderstanding?
What misunderstanding?
The director has come to see my father.
You keep lying. They
They caused me first!
How can you behave
like a schoolgirl?
Fighting? Who has taught you that?
Dad taught me to be brave and
fight when they harassed me
And they treated me unfairly.
When it comes to fighting, I learned from him.
Ah,
However, it is not
As sure as at home.
Girls should learn
Kungfu to defend oneself.
My father told me to defend me,
Do not set up a scene.
How do you dare to threaten the director?
Do you know how much it costs me
Send you here to school?
I don't know anything.
I don't care if your father is he Yinghao.
Now I am still the head of this school.
You are only helping local students
And he doesn't care who is right or not.
You are trying a lot in class
Physical violence, even carrying a gun.
Just because your father has yinghao
It does not mean that you can break the rules.
You should know
I can get you right now.
I don't like that school or
Jiati. I don't even want to live here!
This is your home.
Where are you going? This is not my house!
My house is where my mother is!
I hate this place.
I hate you too. There is no
need to pretend to be a good father.
You are getting more nonsever!
Am I putting the leg?
Have you ever asked me why I have
Stone fighting since I got home?
No, he didn't!
Ping lu is vegetarian and never eats
meat. Did you ever worry about her?
No!
Did you fulfill your promise to accompany me
Today to the sanctuary to pray for mom?
Neither!
You don't care about anyone! You just
You worry about yourself and your business!
Ting, for. I don't mind
the needs of others.
In my father's eyes, everything
It can be solved with money!
Yinghao, control your temperament.
Ting is already an adult.
Do not scold her always like that.
Ping lu,
Remove me a ticket
Airplane for early tomorrow.
I'm going home to see his mother.
Yinghao, / returns to your country.
But business here in
Jiati need to be supervised.
Without you,
I'm afraid ...
Lu ping, warehouse, I
Yinghao, Wu Zheng, He Ting ...
Kun Tai
No!
Dear!
Yinghao He!
Oh!
All our things
They have disappeared.
Everything was confiscated by the police.
A fugitive did it
called Bai An, which came out in the news.
Broke up and
He killed all our members.
I think he called the police.
Bang Long!
You have lost your things,
Do you know the consequences?
Forgive me!
I will replace it. It
I will replace with anything.
How much your life is worth
20 million dollars?
Bang Long!
Where are my things?
There is a problem with
Group HE transport circuit.
Police have confiscated
All our belongings.
Where is that Tai Kun bastard?
What is the use of if you can't
keep things?
I will tell you one thing, Tai Long,
If it weren't for my father
that insisted on taking care
To be a dog,
How could I take care of you to ...
Talk to Yinghao I have tomorrow.
To find Bai An.
Ting, here.
Ting.
My daughter is already older.
What you said last night
Really good!
Today we will see your mother again.
Your mother will be very happy
To see you now.
Yinghao, there are police news.
What's happening?
Police are checking
The drugs of the logistics warehouse.
The test results showed
that drugs this time were the same as
A series of drugs 3 years ago.
After our
private negotiations with the police,
This issue will not be made public for now.
When I am not
Visit to leaders in my name
As a sample of my gratitude.
Do not think about the cost.
OK.
Tingting!
Actually your father cares about you,
Only it is not good demonstrating it.
Dad told you to say that?
You probably don't know
Why value Ping Lu so much, right?
What worries you most is really
the lack of affection
Maternal in your adulthood.
Wu,
Can't you learn to shut up?
Police have begun to identify
Bai an as suspect of the shooting.
Can you drive?
Let's pay!
You are blocking my car on purpose.
There are! Come!
Turn the car around! Covered!
Relief!
Take me!
Are you well?
Keep up alive!
Out! What's happening?
What's happening? Don't move!
Ting!
Tintineando!
We have to talk.
Tingting!
Don't hurt Tingting!
Zheng Wu!
Save Tingting! Lord I!
Dad! Out!
Take me!
Slag!
Let me!
Take me!
Take Tingting
first! Hurry up! Okay!
Come on!
Mr. He! Where is Tingting?
She is fine.
Let's go.
Take me!
Zheng Wu!
I have it!
Come with me or die here.
All to the car!
Come on, quickly, quickly!
No drugs in Jiati!
The demonstration made sense.
The only way is
eradicate completely
This crime of drugs.
Especially the group of
Criminals led by Clay.
Has become
The biggest tumor of our Jiati!
Mr. Congressman, every time
that mentions my name on TV,
It really irritates me.
That's why I have visited you today.
And I brought you a gift.
Let's say you like it,
free!
You don't respect me, don't you think?
Children
Don't worry.
Mother! LAN!
Mother!
It would have been good to do it before.
Mr. Clay.
Mr. Clay. Clay.
Mr. Clay. Clay. Pad yourself!
Please, please let my son go.
I would do anything for you.
Mr. Clay. Clay.
Let's play the game.
Only one of them
You can live.
Who dies, who lives,
You choose.
Or both die.
Xiao di,
Sorry
You are the older brother.
Xiao da! / Da!
This is your father,
a man of good mouth, straight and moral,
But he shot his own son
Go to hell!
I just want to swallow drugs, like a donkey.
Chief, Mr. is here.
Mr. President Yinghao He!
I hope you don't care
come here.
You have brought me here
For drugs, right?
More than that.
I have a better gift for you.
These are all companies
Logistics premises in Jiati.
Signs everything and is yours.
About those 20 million dollars,
I can erase it,
While we work together!
Isn't it a great gift?
What have you been looking forward to?
[Capital Transfer Agreement]
In Jiati,
Only my company is free of inspection.
You should appreciate it.
TRUE?
I don't want to sign,
even if you kill me.
Mr. President He,
You mean more for me.
If you die,
The group will be
useless for me.
But your daughter is different.
Bastard! Don't hurt my daughter!
Hey?
I have met you
At the school door.
You...
You are the fugitive of the news!
Police began to identify
BAI AN AS SUSPECH OF THE TIRTY ...
You killed your wife and daughter. Be quiet!
It was your father who killed them.
That is impossible.
You don't know anything about your family, huh?
I would not trust a fugitive.
Without me, you are dead.
It really isn't yours.
Out of here!
Long here!
Thanks for saving me!
Zheng Wu!
What's happening?
Don't ask questions! Listen to me.
Did Tingting called you or went home?
No, he didn't.
What happened?
I think we receive
Drug poster reprisals.
Mr. have brought it.
The others are dead.
And Tingting?
Zheng Wu, you are an idiot! Only
You are in charge of security,
You can't protect anyone!
Now you shut up!
I lost them, and I will risk my
life to find them again.
Now check the camera
CCTV at the door of the Jiati school.
The time: yesterday afternoon.
I stopped the man who wore his hat.
Who is that guy?
It is nobody.
Send me the video.
Zheng Wu, listen to me, don't
You spoil! The police are here.
Note that the car route is to
Your captain.
Who else knows? /
No one except the Captain.
He only told us before leaving.
Mrs. Ping Lu. This is ting he.
Tingting!
Tingting, where are you now? Are you OK?
All good? I'm fine.
I don't know where this is.
OK.
Listen to me,
From now on,
Do not trust anyone.
Including zheng wu,
I see? I am not sure at this time.
But before leaving,
No one knows where you go, except him.
Tingting, now you have to find
The closest safe place and hide.
Now I pick you up.
Do you have it? I have it.
Aid!
Chinese girl? I am Yinghao's daughter.
I was kidnapped, I just escaped.
Yinghao's daughter?
Now you are safe.
I will take you to the police station.
Let's go.
I was calling my family.
They will pick me up, don't worry.
I will call your family when
Let's get to the police station.
Let's go.
Be careful!
Hi sir.
I am the patrol officer PDJ-663.
She is the daughter of the Group He.
Beautiful.
We receive the call and the police
I was looking for it in the streets.
Everyone is prepared here.
Take it easy. You can come back.
Yes sir.
Headquarters!
Don't move!
You can no longer flee.
Vouchers 1 million dollars.
Hello.
I just need an answer.
Who has put you in this?
There was ... someone who offered
A reward. All of the
Black Market knows what
It is worth 1 million.
But I don't know who paid him.
How did you find me?
We are looking for this
public telephone and we find you.
Is he dead? Just fainted.
Let's go.
Why are you there?
I'm sorry.
Are you well?
Since we met
At the school door
Have you been spying on me?
I don't know who else can I trust.
The kidnappers are already preparing.
But only Zheng Wu knew the route.
Also, Miss Ping Lu.
I just called her tonight.
We can work together.
Eat and hide first.
Don't you want to avenge you? But you
You don't know where my father is.
I will locate it.
So why don't you ask me?
What are you talking about?
I also want to find it.
Thus our goal is the same,
So, why don't we cooperate?
You should know what that means.
I know.
Sure you will need me.
But you have to stay safe.
If we find it
Then, that is another story.
Do you really want me to kill him?
Because?
Drugs killed my mother.
My father and I hate
Drugs more than anything.
Sure
That was not my father
who killed your family.
And I'm sure no
You would kill innocent people for nothing.
Or you will not save me
twice.
You are nothing more than a problem.
No, I'm not a problem.
Right now I am your only track.
I found the person you mentioned.
His name is Bai An. It is a fugitive.
Is he who brought to Tingting?
It wasn't her.
Listen!
Start now,
If ting is looking for you,
Let me know immediately.
But,
You will kill him. What do you mean?
I'm going to pick up Tingting right now.
I don't have time to tell you.
You don't have to come here.
He is gone.
I think it's a drug problem.
Before leaving, I heard me
Father talking to them.
Dad threw a group of people
of that company 3 years ago
for drug smuggling.
Police proved drugs
of the logistics warehouse.
The test results showed that
Drugs this time are
the same as 3 years ago.
I have heard that everyone has left prison
And they became a group of
bandits They would do anything for money.
This is the logistics point where they work.
There must still be files about
They on the supervisor's computer.
Surely
Do you know it like us?
At least they must know something.
I will enter and make fun of the guards
security Then you enter.
Aid! Help me.
Help me!
What's happening? I am Yinghao's daughter.
I am fleeing from the kidnapper.
Enter.
According to
Latest police news,
2 bodies were
found on the scene. One
of them was an officer
of the Jiati patrol,
{While the other was a
Killer disguised as a police.
There was no trace of the kidnapped girl.
of the family I have in the crime scene.
Other information about this case.
It still does not exist.
Miss Ting He,
How did he escape the kidnappers?
There it is.
Who is that?
Looking for death, huh?
This Betel nut mask
He is the intellectual author of dismissal.
I remember your nickname well.
They are interconnected.
Tell me, where can I find it?
I don't know what he's talking about. Where
Can I find that Areca nut?
In the traditional market of
Les. It is a complicated place
Even the police are afraid to go there.
They can kill you there.
You will be like this mobile phone
If you tell other people.
He said ... what did he say?
I don't understand...
That bag must be your precious possession.
Of course.
It is my mother's birthday gift.
Although the color is a bit horta,
I will continue carrying it.
Don't girls like pink?
That is just an assumption.
Does the girls have to like pink?
It doesn't matter, it's going fashionable, okay?
When you grow, do you
Will others really import?
Happy Birthday!
I love you, dad
I have my own mobile phone.
No, Dad?
An ugly neon pink color? My
companions will laugh at me.
Traditional market Lese
Boom
The other men we are looking for ...
Give me the money! I'm going to enter.
And you stay here.
Wait.
These people are traffickers
of low level drugs,
They are usually very vigilant.
In case of any omen
unusual, they will disappear,
So they are difficult to find.
It will be better than between. They must recognize me.
I am not a threat to them.
No! Don't do that.
It is too dangerous.
You protect me.
Is that true?
Hey Calvito, take me with that
Betel nut mask.
Who are you, boy? Go from here!
I am Yinghao's daughter.
Valgo 1 million dollars.
Chief, boss! It is really her.
Come with me.
What are you looking at?
What are you waiting for? Take it out of
here and dissect your stomach
And try to save drugs
before it becomes Tai.
For!
Do not hold it.
Let him enter.
Take it back! Ah,
You can't bring this. Tea
I will return it when you leave.
Indeed, she is Yinghao's daughter.
Nak,
what do you want?
Of me?
I'm here for
Make a deal with you.
I want you to help me save my father.
Why should I help you?
Do you know that your father fired me?
And he jailed me?
I will give you 2 million dollars
If you help me.
Breathe!
Where is Bai An?
I really don't know.
We are only colleagues.
After his family was killed
It disappeared suddenly.
Chief, boss!
We have found man.
It is close.
The one who brought your father
It was Clay.
It is that
The great drug boss!
You want me to fight against him
With only 2 million dollars?
Actually, about Clay,
Your father would know better than me.
During the last three years,
Clay's goods have been sent
Through its channels
LOGISTICS.- It can't be!
How can my father be
involved with a drug boss?
I will not give you the difficult things,
If you take me home safe 2
Millions of dollars are yours.
I don't want 2 million dollars.
All I am doing is to take you,
And your family is paying for it.
Whatever I want. A
Once you get the money,
I will send you to Clay.
You are like a cashier
Automatic sent to us.
[Without signal]
Back!
Fuck...
Prace it! Take me!
Let you fuck you!
Do you know the value of these drugs?
With what hand have you
thrown? Put it on the table
And cut it right now!
Are you not afraid that Clay Mate?
Of course I'm afraid.
But I'm more afraid of no
Ear money for the rest of my life.
There must be another life after my death.
Nothing can prevent me
Ear money in this life.
Son of a bitch!
Bai an!
Are you well?
Shit!
Go back. Back or the killing!
You are lucky that
It has worked this time.
Next time, give it a
kick in the groin. Do not bite!
Do you have it?
Where can I find Clay?
OK,
Out of the city, the center of
Clay's drugs is out of the city.
Your father must be there.
The headquarters was closed. Only
The delivery man named Uncle Jiu
that could come and go at will.
He is one of Clay's confidants.
Outside the city has ...
The old Jiati hotel. That is your place.
You will die if you go there.
Come on!
Skip! I can't, I'm not Tony Jaa!
For!
Do you want to keep running?
Make it!
Leave it to me. I will let you live.
Good!
I love it!
Unfortunately,
You ruined my makeup.
Bai an!
Go away!
Forward!
For! For!
Take me!
Tingting, come here!
Tingting,
Why are you silent?
From now on, do not trust anyone.
Tingting, Ting He!
Tingting!
Tingting, why do you run?
Bai an! Don't kill him.
Tingting, you can't go with him.
He is a wanted criminal.
Bai an!
Let's go!
I will kill you.
I kill you!
Are you well?
I'm going to take you to the doctor right now. No!
We get too much attention,
This is still the
Gangsters place.
You can't do that.
You will die if you do nothing.
I have an idea.
Is there anyone inside? Open the door!
One moment! Why do you hit the door?
Do you know what time is it?
Why disturb my
dream? Doctor, help it.
Why don't you go to the hospital?
See what I am doing here.
Animal care. I am veterinarian.
The veterinarians are still
doctors We can help animals
and treat humans.
Calm, calm, calm. He is a little sick.
Breathe!
Already.
Veterinary clinic
Believe,
It is no longer critical.
Why sweat continues
cold? The wound is infected,
So there are symptoms of fever.
Then give him some medicine.
Look, what I have here
Medicine for cats, dogs,
Even pigs, so ...
Thank you. This is my job.
Where to Old Jiati Motel?
What ... / Where
Is the old Jiati motel?
That is easy.
From the exit here, turn right.
Crossing three roads. He
place is at the intersection.
But what do I know,
It is not a good place.
Anu ...
This is the doctor's work!
The doctor's duty!
Accept it! I will kill you
If you tell someone else.
Thank you.
Thank you!
Magic touch!
Old Motel Jiati
Is there anyone there?
Would you like to stay here?
Teach me the identity card!
Lady,
My father is sick.
We have come to see a doctor.
I have stolen my portfolio and documents,
except a little money
that remains. Please help us.
They do not seem father and daughter.
I understand.
Your mother is a foreigner, right?
Yeah.
My mother is foreign.
My father is from here.
Generally,
Standard room $ 20 per night. But
You did not bring your identification card.
It's hard for me.
Turn right to the stairs.
Thank you.
Hello, uncle Jiu!
It has appeared.
When to look for Uncle Jiu?
Wait here.
It will appear.
This is the city.
Eat this.
Mom taught me
Eating sweets will be better
When you are injured.
Bai an.
I have a question for you.
Just ask.
Is my father really
A drug dealer?
Because?
Why questions now?
Don't know.
I believe him.
But now you are not just you,
Even the man who chewed nuts
Betel called him drug trafficker.
I don't know who to trust.
As if my father was not
The man who used to meet.
Bai an!
Yes, I mean yes
It was my father who hurt your family,
Do you want to promise me?
Bai an!
The one who always sleeps is my father.
This time you will work on the turn of
night and cannot come home with us.
We go to the airport.
Dinner is ready. You
Favorite Thai rice.
Take this to the office and
Hear it before eating.
Take.
Dad,
This. / Mother!
Mom ... and / Me!
Ok, let's go.
Let's kill him!
Forward!
Where is Clay's drug base?
Tell me!
In the forest near the
May River Embarcadero.
All drugs are sent from there.
I know you're good fighting.
But you should give yourself.
Police can control
To the ordinary people,
But they can't control him
him. It will not be sure there.
Bai an!
Bai an! Are you well?
Let's see Clay.
Come on
I have finally found you.
I can't wait
To return all these wounds.
Bai an!
Help it! Bai an!
Tingting, are you okay?
Help Bai An! Tingting, come with me.
I will take Bai An. Are you
crazy? He will kill your father.
Bai an!
Come on! Out of here!
Come on! Don't move!
Listen to yourself.
Everyone is here.
Please do not hurt us.
No!
Dear!
Don't leave dad.
Please.
No!
How is it?
For!
You're crazy?
If it weren't for Zheng Wu,
We would be dead.
How have you found us?
Staying at a hotel and
performing suture surgery
He has already revealed his whereabouts.
Many talk about
both in the black market.
Before, my men reported
Tingting called Ping Lu.
I followed the GPS.
But I arrived too late.
I just found the body of
A false police in place.
So, just like you,
I tried to find the whereabouts of Mr. He.
I even investigated its former employees
that became smugglers
After being fired from the company.
Then I found man
I chewed Betel nuts.
Captain, we find
I have retained the lady
For Betel's men.
And you know what happened.
What is this place?
This is my safe house.
Your Kung fu is quite good.
Seems
You have a very different past.
I return this.
You cannot turn this into a toy.
I did not mean that,
He fell.
Let's look for your father.
It is safer here.
Zheng Wu will find my father.
You must recover from your wounds.
Bai an!
Can't be reckless? The
Traffickers are many and powerful.
You are alone and wounded. It is the same
than to endanger your life.
You did not challenge me
When I saved you from the mafia
You used me from the beginning.
Because you have a new protector
You don't need me anymore
We have finished.
I did not mean that.
I am worried about you. You alone
You are worried about your father.
I have heard everything about you.
I will investigate it.
The fact is that Yinghao
I killed my family.
My wife worked in the
Group I for 8 years.
And a few days ago
He said he returned to his country.
Honey, you are
behaving strangely.
Something happens?
Please tell me.
You can always trust me, okay?
Don't worry,
I just ask for your permission.
We will wait for you to return home.
Then I found out
All because my wife found evidence
Yinghao I trafficked with drugs.
That's why they killed him.
Everything is here. Please,
Please do not harm us.
Where is the copy? No!
This pendrive,
Contains tests
And that's why he killed my family
Impossible!
There is nothing that I hate more than drugs.
It will never touch drugs.
It doesn't matter!
I have found an offer of
Gift on Tai Kun's mobile
To kill my wife. And all the clues
They lead to Yinghao He.
Hi, Tai Kun.
Why aren't you here
still? I am here with the money!
And before you kill me
I will kill him with my own hands!
Come on! Get me up!
Come on! Come on!
Zheng Wu.
Because you saved Tingting's life,
I will not kill you.
But do not reappear in front of me.
Bai an!
Are you well?
I will let it go
When you bring your father back.
Ting he,
I think you worry
more for him than for your father.
Tingting
How are you? Are you OK? I'm fine.
ASA, how has you get here?
Why didn't you tell me
Have you found Tingting?
I manage almost everything in the company.
Do you think they dare to disobey me?
Tingting, come home with me.
No! I'm not home.
I'm going to look for my father. Your father.
Mr. have you found it?
Clay Group is the culprit.
I think it's for drugs that
The police seized the last time.
It is not so simple.
There are traitors within the company
They traffic with drugs in secret.
Bai An's woman was killed
Because he found evidence of it.
Traitor?
And definitely a member of the nucleus.
Don't move!
ASA, what are you doing?
Lower your weapon. Or I will kill them.
Due.
Take Mr. Clay. Clay.
I take care of this.
Take me! Take me! Tingting!
Take me! Tingting!
Tingting!
Take me!
Handle
When did you start?
That is no longer important, right?
Okay, ASA.
You better run away from me later.
You will not have time anymore.
Life and death are
determined by destiny.
Wealth and position
They are a thing of destiny.
Don't blame me. I only give my life.
Who the hell is you?
I'm just a ghost
who lost his family.
Why sacrifice your life?
I received money from the family I,
And I struggled for them. That
It is easy to understand.
And you?
The same as you. They also pay me.
I think the steak knows better
If little is done,
You may have flavor to
blood is little done,
and gets too hard
If it is too cooked.
I guess it's the same as humans.
What is the key?
The key is the time.
It will not look good
When they are offended between them.
I have reached my limit.
And there really is no more
Just tell me the good, Mr. He. He.
You can't eat like food
nor spend it as money.
By the way, Mr. He,
My clients abroad continue
Anxiously waiting for my shipments.
Tingting! Are you OK?
Tingting!
What do you want?
Mr. He, signs the contract.
I will let him go and also guarantee him
There is no problem.
For the whole group I from now on.
Otherwise ... I will sign it!
So
Mr. He, you are really a wise man.
Come on, health!
That our cooperation
pleasant.
Health, health. Wait a minute.
The person who made disappear
Our things is called Bai An.
It seems to be
An ordinary warehouse guard.
But before that
He was a specialist
Professional in Security.
What are you talking about?
Bai an that has been
protecting the girl,
But she was looking for a chance
To kill Yinghao He.
I have lost 20 million dollars.
Is that all you have for me?
I will tell you one thing, Tai Long,
If it weren't for my father.
He insisted on treating you like a dog.
Then I will not take care
From you until today. Understood?
You are lower than a dog.
Clean.
Soon we will have guests.
OK.
Intruder!
Find it!
Interesting.
The men who house a
deep hatred have compassion
for the enemy of his daughter.
Let's play the game.
Matter it,
And I'll let this girl go.
Your game stinks!
Interesting
Maybe we can be friends.
I'm not looking for friends.
Let them leave!
We will not be enemies.
Enemies?
Not just you.
Over there!
Inside!
Apparently
I have underestimated you.
You don't deserve to be my enemy.
I'm sorry, we couldn't gather
To your family at that time.
What do you mean?
Before dying, that Clay's bastard
It was all alcohol and women.
I did everything,
including your family.
What disappointment,
Now you can meet your family.
Bai an!
Get out of there!
Dad!
Tai Long! Release Tingting!
Release Tingting!
I can give you anything. What do you think?
Tingting! Never
be the only one
that can survive in this world. A
Load too heavy on your shoulders.
To save her, you must commit suicide!
This is the time!
Next time
Pate on the
crotch. Do not bite!
Bai an!
Bai an,
I have never hurt your family,
And I hate drugs more than anything.
If they won't threaten me using tingting,
I will not compromise.
I trust your daughter,
as much as in you.
Thanks, An!
Actually, you don't know
How much I envy your daughter right now.
You can leave everything for them
To fight the world.
During this time
I think I've never felt the
love of a father like now.
But now I realize
that my father is the same as you.
He always loved me with all his heart
Although the sacrifice was great.
There is no father who does not
Be a hero for his daughter.
And when the time comes
that's the most difficult
Bai an.
Thank you.
Who are you? What do you want?
Have you ever seen a butterfly
trapped in a spider web?
They believe they can escape
Because your skin is squamous.
But sometimes they can't escape.
I don't know what you're talking about.
You are playing with fire,
You are on fire!
Who are you?
I had never seen you before.
You know my wife and my daughter, right?
Do you really think you can get out with
yours after everything you have done?
When Ting I first called you
You were you who
The idea happened first.
We find Ting He.
I gave the false police the
information about ting he,
I killed him after he failed.
Talk to Zheng Wu of this false police.
Then use Zheng to locate us.
Miss Lu, we find
Ting He. It is in that safe house.
You made two plans. Don't move!
Pretend that they have caught you.
Then what happens happens,
It will not affect you.
But you forgot that I was there.
I saw you carrying ASA.
I have followed your order
Like employees
They helped you to traffic with drugs.
I was trapped in the cloth of a spider.
But Tai Long
It wasn't the spider that caught me.
Lord is your web.
10 years have passed since
I followed this foreign land.
But I could never be myself.
It's as if they were caught
within the body of
A woman forever.
Ting I will never accept me.
I am only a substitute.
So you used Tai Long
To get rid of Mr. He
And he used you to kill Clay.
My wife, my family
They crossed your way,
Then you destroyed my family
If you want to blame me,
Kake your family for crossing my limits.
It seems that he has rejected you.
Let's not let everything ruin.
I just want to accept my
destiny with my own hands.
Have I been wrong?
The group will always belong to He.
I was so close to getting it
all. But you ruined everything!
You ruined it!
My family did not interfere in that!
What are you doing?
What are you doing? No!
Hang on a minute. Don't kill me!
Listen to me, I was wrong.
Please forgive me. No
I should have hurt the child
And to your wife. Don't kill me.
Please forgive me. I beg you.
Please! Forgive me!
I didn't have ...
My wife and daughter are good people.
They forgive you.
But,
I don't forgive. Money!
I can give you a lot of money, a lot of money!
Don't kill me please, don't kill me!
It's about Yinghao He.
Yinghao has forced me to do this.
He forced me to do this.
By no means!
There is a Chinese saying,
the disturbance of the
nature can endure you,
Ask me yourself.
You
You've ruined.
Don't kill me.
You have a minute to say goodbye.
No!
Don't go.
Are you listening, Yinghao?
Sorry, Yinghao. Sorry, Tingting.
It has been my fault.
I'm sorry
I'm
I want too much. This is me.
This is my fault. No
I should have done this.
Can you forgive me?
Tingting? Yinghao?
The one who always sleeps is my father.
This time you will work on the turn of
night and cannot come home with us.
We go to the airport.
I have prepared dinner.
Your favorite dish is
Thai fried rice.
Bring it to the office and
Hear it before eating.
Dad / dad and?
Mother!
AND? I!
OK.
After that, Bai An voluntarily delivered and delivered the
evidence collected to the Police of the Republic of Ballyvina.
With the support and accusation of several criminal evidence, the
Criminal Group of Clay was thoroughly exterminated by the police.
Lu Ping was punished and sanctioned by the Local Police of
in accordance with the law for crimes as intentional injuries,
smuggling, traffic of
people and drug transport.
All employees involved in the smuggling of the
Group I were also arrested by the police.
Bai an received punishment and sanctions
legal adequate for their illegal behavior.
The Heshi group has fulfilled its promise and has provided
Commercial aid to the Republic of Ballyvina.